<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zp Guide</string>
    <string name="title_activity_more_info">More info..</string>
    <string name="imgDescr">Small preview of sight</string>
    <!--__________________Categories_____________________-->
    <string name="food">Cafes&amp;Restaurants</string>
    <string name="nightlife">Nightlife</string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums&amp;Attraction</string>
    <string name="entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="gyms">Gyms</string>

    <!--__________________More Activity_____________________-->
    <string name="map">View on map..</string>


    <!--__________________Museums fragment_____________________-->
    <!-- Hortica -->
    <string name="name_Hortica">Khortitsa National Nature Reserve</string>

    <!--__________________Hotels fragment_____________________-->
    <!--  "Intourist Hotel" -->
    <string name="intouristhotel_name">Intourist Hotel</string>
    <string name="intouristhotel_adr">Sobornyi Ave 135, Zaporozhye, 69005, Ukraine</string>
    <string name="intouristhotel_phone">-</string>
    <string name="intouristhotel_about">Intourist is a business hotel located in the centre of
        Zaporozhye near the Dnieper River. It offers spacious accommodations, a business centre, and
        free Wi-Fi.\n\nEach room comes equipped with cable TV and a minibar. Rooms at Intourist
        Hotel also have private bathrooms with hairdryers. Some rooms have large windows and views
         of Lenin Prospect.\n\nThere is also a Ukrainian restaurant and Lobby bar on site.
        A complimentary buffet breakfast is also provided.\n\nIntourist Hotel is a 12-minute drive
        from Khortytsia Island. Private and secure parking facilities are available upon request.
        \n\nCouples particularly like the location — they rated it 8.3 for a two-person trip.
        \n\nWe speak your language!</string>
    <!--  "Soborniy Hotel" -->
    <string name="soborniyhotel_name">Soborniy Hotel</string>
    <string name="soborniyhotel_adr">Sobornyi Ave 28, Zaporozhye, 69063, Ukraine</string>
    <string name="soborniyhotel_phone">-</string>
    <string name="soborniyhotel_about">This hotel in the centre of Zaporozhye has free fenced parking and free Wi-Fi. It is a 5-minute walk from Zaporozhye Local History Museum.\n
                        \nThe rooms at the Soborniy Hotel feature warm colours and large windows. Safety deposit boxes, bathrobes and slippers are provided.\n
                        \nSoborniy’s seasonal spa area features a pool and a sauna. Guests can also book massages.\n
                        \nMeal delivery is provided upon request. A range of drinks are on offer in the hotel bar.\n
                        \nZaporozhye-2 Train Station is a 10-minute walk from the Soborniy Hotel. \n
                        \nCouples particularly like the location — they rated it 8.6 for a two-person trip.\n
                        \nThis property is also rated for the best value in Zaporozhye! Guests are
        getting more for their money when compared to other properties in this city.</string>
    <!-- "Teatralniy Hotel" -->
    <string name="teatralniyhotel_name">Teatralniy Hotel</string>
    <string name="teatralniyhotel_adr">Troitskaya St. 23 , Zaporozhye, 69063, Ukraine</string>
    <string name="teatralniyhotel_phone">-</string>
    <string name="teatralniyhotel_about">Just 100 m from the Magara Theatre, this bright and modern
        hotel offers a central location in Zaporozhye. Free parking, soundproofed rooms and an
        international restaurant are featured here.\n\nTeatralniy Hotel’s elegant rooms have rich
        carpet flooring, a flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi.\n\nA buffet breakfast with hot and cold
        dishes is provided every morning at Teatralniy. International and Ukrainian cuisine is
        served in the restaurant, and a range of drinks are available at the lobby bar. Breakfast
        is included in the price.\n\nGuests can reach all parts of the city from Zaporozhye
        Train Station, a 10-minute walk away. Zaporozhye Airport is 12 km from the hotel, and a
        shuttle service is available. \n\nThis property also has one of the best-rated locations
        in Zaporozhye! Guests are happier about it compared to other properties in the area.\n\n
        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.0 for a two-person trip.\n\n
        This property is also rated for the best value in Zaporozhye! Guests are getting more for
        their money when compared to other properties in this city.
                </string>

    <!--Khortitsa Palace Hotel-->
    <string name="khorticahotel_name">Khortitsa Palace Hotel</string>
    <string name="khorticahotel_adr">Shevchenko avenue 71A, Zaporozhye, 69091, Ukraine</string>
    <string name="khorticahotel_phone">-</string>
    <string name="khorticahotel_about">This property is 4 minutes walk from the beach. Just a
        5-minute drive from the Zaporozhye city centre, Khortitsa Palace Hotel features an on-site
        shop, modern rooms with free Wi-Fi.\n\nAll the spacious, air-conditioned rooms have a
        seating area. Some rooms have a balcony with a city or river view.\n\nThe modern Flavours
        restaurant serves Ukrainian and European cuisine. Drinks can be enjoyed at the 2 bars and
        on the summer terrace.\n\Leisure facilities at Khortitsa Palace Hotel include a sauna,
        a steam room and a fitness centre. There is a 24-hour reception.\n\nThe Bulvar Shevtchenko
        Bus Stop is a 2-minute walk from the hotel and the railway station is only 20 minutes by
        car. Airport Zaporozhye is 20 km away.
                </string>
    <!--Prague Hotel-->
    <string name="praguehotel_name">Prague Hotel</string>
    <string name="praguehotel_adr">Shevchenko Boulevard 28 , Zaporozhye, 69001, Ukraine</string>
    <string name="praguehotel_phone">-</string>
    <string name="praguehotel_about">This property is 12 minutes walk from the beach. Featuring
        free Wi-Fi and free private parking, this hotel is located in Zaporizhzhya city, 12 minutes
        walk from the central Prospekt Lenina. It also offers free daily bottle of water in the rooms.\n
        \nEach air-conditioned room at Prague Hotel is decorated in a classic style and includes a
        fridge. A hairdryer is provided in the bathrooms.\n\nA daily breakfast is served in the
        dining room of Prague, and several restaurants offering Ukrainian and European cuisines
        can be found within a 5-minute walk of the hotel.\n\nZaporizhzhya city centre with the
        City Park are 7 km from Prague Hotel, while Zaporizhzhya 1 Train Station is 16 minutes
        drive away. It is 19 km from Zaporizhzhya Airport.
                </string>
    <!--SUNRISE Park-->
    <string name="sunricsehotel_name">SUNRISE Park</string>
    <string name="sunricsehotel_adr">ул. Глиссерная, 1 А, Zaporozhye, 69002, Ukraine</string>
    <string name="sunricsehotel_phone">-</string>
    <string name="sunricsehotel_about">SUNRISE Park offers accommodation in Zaporozhye. The hotel has a children\'s playground and terrace, and guests can enjoy a meal at the restaurant. Free WiFi is available throughout the property and free private parking is available on site.
\n\n
Every room is equipped with a flat-screen TV with satellite channels. Each room comes with a private bathroom with a bath or shower and bidet, with slippers and free toiletries provided.
\n\n
There is a 24-hour front desk at the property. Banquet facilities, a seasonal terrace and a hookah lounge are featured. Bike hire is also available.
\n\n
Zaporizhia Airport is 13 km away. Zaporizhia Train Station is 11 km from the property.
                </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
